Joshua Stevens

I'm a highly creative and proficient digital creator who's capable of designing engaging UI and UX experiences as well as coding the front-end to bring designs to life. Exceptional interpersonal skills, work ethic and an eager-to-learn attitude have propelled my career.

Experience

Driver's Alert - Nashville TN / Deerfield Beach FL

Director, Content Development

4/2014 - Present

Lead a team of designers and developers to create eLearning content using modern web technology. Recently, I designed the UI/UX for a web app and devloped it using React & Redux to optimize and enhance courses for use on mobile devices. I've progressed from Art Director to the department Director in my time at Driver's Alert.

Dataium - Nashville TN

Senior Graphic Designer

2/2013 - 4/2014

Led a branding redesign that increased brand awareness and created an energetic, tech-driven image for the company. Created digital and print assets, and maintained and updated the company WordPress site.

GannettLocal - Nashville TN

Website Designer

6/2012 - 2/2013

Established myself as the go-to-designer for custom websites and landing pages, and helped sales procure some of the company's largest contracts.

UL PureSafety - Franklin TN

Content Developer

4/2010 - 6/2012

One of the top producing course developers, I established myself as the lead developer for projects that required advanced interactive features or troubleshooting.

Wingenuity - Bristol IN

Web & Graphic Designer

1/2008 - 4/2010

Learned the ropes of code and design by working directly with clients, creating custom web designs, logos and print pieces.

615.618.0030

joshua@joshuastevensdesign.com

Skills & Knowledge

{ Code & Tech }

HTML5, CSS, SASS, JavaScript (ES6), jQuery, React, JSX, Webpack, PHP, WordPress, Craft, ExpressionEngine.

{ Design }

Sketch, Adobe CC, especially Illustrator, Photoshop & XD.

View My Work

joshuastevens.dribbble.com behance.net/joshuastevens jstevens79.github.io

Education

Vanderbilt Full-Stack Bootcamp

Certificate: 2019

Nossi College of Art

Graphic Design

Courses taken: 2009

